broadcast tonight high stakes Salt Lake meeting tonight at the White House the president of congressional leaders face to face Americans in crease in leaf at up
今晚播出高风险盐湖城会议今晚在白宫国会领导人的总裁面对面美国人在折痕叶中高达
Church Fathers collide with the tractor trailer there are many Denninger tragedy on the highway in Tennessee
教父碰撞与拖拉机拖车也有很多的Denninger悲剧在高速公路上在田纳西州
the FBI heroin cocaine murder-for-hire they say all available on 1zz access website
联邦调查局海洛因可卡因谋杀为聘用他们说所有可用的1ZZ访问网站
chase news tonight about the video getting so much attention the scary scene on New York Road
追新闻今晚对视频得到这么多的关注在纽约道可怕的一幕
call so tonight that the one of the best selling authors of all time news begins now
致电所以今晚，在所有时间新闻最畅销的作家之一现在开始
New York NBC Nightly News with Brian Williams
纽约NBC晚间新闻与布赖恩·威廉斯
talked into the night tonight in Washington but nothings moving the shutdown continue so does the anger across the country the frustration with Congress the President or earlier today expressed his exasperation of the defiance in DC
聊到深夜，今晚在华盛顿，但没有任何事情动关机继续做并愤怒在全国范围内与国会或总统今天早些时候的挫折表达了他对特区的蔑视愤怒
it's where we begin tonight with NBC's Chuck Todd he is in the briefing room in the West Wing where were still expecting the president will speak about today's meeting jacket eBay
这就是我们今晚开始，NBC的查托德，他在简报室中的西翼，其中仍然期待总统将谈到今天的会议外套易趣
what we do Brian good evening the meeting with congressional leaders is over we heard from one of the participants Speaker Boehner just
我们做什么布赖恩晚上好与国会领导人在会议结束我们从参与者议长博纳的人听到刚
I went to the microphones outside of the West Wing here and he said
我去了西永外的麦克风这里，他说：
polite conversation but he said the president reiterated that he would not negotiate when it comes to the health care law for either the budget or when it comes to the debt ceiling
礼貌的谈话，但他说，布什总统重申，当涉及到保健法无论是预算或当它涉及到债务上限，他不会谈判
Anne frankly its the same thing in many ways the president said you are colleagues NBC's John Harwood in an interview earlier today take a listen
安妮坦言其同样的事情在许多方面，总统说你今天早些时候是同事NBC的约翰·哈伍德在接受采访时一起来聆听
and I am I transfer an absolute limit aspirin because this is entirely in the sitter
而我我转的绝对限制阿司匹林，因为这完全是在保姆
will the situation right now where is John Boehner the Speaker of the House puts a bill on the floor to reopen the government at Kroger
会的情况，现在那里是约翰·博纳的众议院议长提出的法案在地板上重新打开政府在克罗格
levels
水平
Brian the bottom line is there's not a lot of getting on the Nikon vs officially going home for the night but the house and the Senate this thing is going to go on for days
布莱恩底线是有没有一个得到很多关于尼康与正式回家过夜，但众议院和参议院这个东西是要继续的天
virgin to both the debt limit is you said earlier we do expect to hear from the president sometime tonight on his take on the meeting that did last over an hour
处女无论对债务上限就是你刚才说我们不期望从总统今晚，听取了他对过去一个多小时的做了一段时间的会议
Chuck Todd the White House for us tonight Chuck thanks a course the ripple effect of all of this the impact is being felt right now across this country by millions of Americans in all walks of life MBCC Anyang
查托德白宫为我们今晚查克非常感谢当然，所有这方面的影响已经被感觉到，现在在这个国家由生活MBCC安阳各界数以百万计的美国人的涟漪效应
has just a few of the many examples tonight
有很多例子，短短今晚
I think it's ridiculous
我认为这是荒谬的
Hollister WCCO radio chat Hartmann show in Minneapolis today did
今天在明尼阿波利斯霍利斯特WCCO电台聊天哈特曼做展示
Knothole back who are you most upset with I definitely blame the Republicans or Democrats
楼板回到谁是你最底价与我绝对责怪共和党或民主党
I am so chic jobs at the Tea Party
我在茶党那么潇洒职位
on day 2 of the government shut down and around the country rises as the impacts friends at the National Institute of Health outside Washington Neely three quarters of the staff is on follow them is turning away about 200 patients a week for last resort medical treatment
对政府2日关闭，并在全国各地上升为影响朋友在美国国立卫生研究院华盛顿尼利之外四分之三的员工是跟着他们每周大约200名病人转身离开的最后一招就医
including about 30 children most of the cancer patients
其中包括约30名儿童大部分的癌症患者
depend on government programs on my federal employees affecting government contractor
依靠在我的联邦雇员影响政府承办政府项目
Joshua Moore Hill have find girls and zero pay
约书亚·摩尔山已发现女孩和零薪酬
The Moron from Wright Patterson Air Force Base outside Dayton Ohio
从赖特 - 帕特森空军俄亥俄州代顿以外相应的白痴
just because our paychecks top of amenable stop
只是因为服从停止我们的薪水最高
there still trying to recover from losing 6 days paid each because of the sequester
还有尝试，因为死骨的从失去高薪每组6天内痊愈
even if we end up getting reimbursed for the time of day to late and we need money now
即使我们最终得到报销一天到晚的时间，我们现在需要钱
something like 7 month old Harpers $300 emergency room visit this weekend for an ear infection could be a financial disaster a hard reality they like Congress to understand
东西像7个月大的哈珀斯300美元急诊室就诊本周末耳朵感染可能是一个金融灾难，他们喜欢美国国会了解残酷的现实
Ison pay the price because you can't agree
伊森付出代价，因为你可以不同意
frustration growing in families paying the price for gridlock in Washington
挫折中成长付出的家庭在华盛顿的价格僵局
John yang NBC News Chicago
约翰·杨NBC新闻芝加哥
today by the way the White House and it still trying to fix the glitch is a lot of people are in countering is the try to sign up for the private health insurance using the new online exchange is there still been a traffic jam especially those 36 states were the federal what side is the only option
今天顺便说一下白宫，它仍然试图修复故障是很多人都在打击是尝试注册时使用新的在线交流的私人医疗保险的还有一直堵车特别是那些36个州是联邦哪一方是唯一的选择
White House says more than 6 million people have tried to log on us far we don't know how many of them have managed to enroll we do know a lot of them are seeing the same frustrating screen message reads we have a lot of visitors on the site right now please stay on this page
白宫说，有超过600万人曾尝试登录我们到目前为止我们不知道有多少人已成功报名参加我们知道很多的人都看到了同样令人沮丧的屏幕贺电，我们有很多游客在该网站现在请留此页面上
the White House is also promising their adding more capacity
白宫也有为自己增加更多的容量
there's been a terrible accident involving a church boss on Tennessee's I 40 the boss filled with seniors crashed into a semi and an SUV at least a tard add more than a dozen injured we got a late report tonight from NBC's Tom Costello
有过一次可怕的事故涉及的教堂老板在田纳西州的我40老板充满了前辈撞向半和SUV至少tard新增超过12人受伤，我们得到了一个迟到的报告今晚从NBC的汤姆·科斯特洛
on I 40 81 north eastern Tennessee smoke fire and miles of back up state trooper St George bus blue tire and cross the median slamming into a tractor trailer in sports
在我40 81东北田纳西烟火灾和备份州警察公里圣乔治总线蓝色轮胎和交叉的中间撞进牵引车体育
loud boom
大声热潮
explosion
爆炸
and I was 7 miles away
而我是7英里远
8 people are known dead including 6 senior citizens on the church bus to come from a jubilee gathering in Gatlinburg Tennessee returning home to Statesville North Carolina the people who live on i-40 city of precious lately
8人被称为死亡，包括教堂总线上的6老人来自禧年聚集在田纳西州加特林堡回国斯泰北卡罗来纳谁住在I-40城市珍贵的最近的人
6 month
6个月
in this area
在这方面
after a series of horrific bus crashes in recent years in Bowling does a fatalities Department of Transportation begin cracking down on bus operators
经过一系列的可怕的总线崩溃近年来在保龄球做运输的死亡系开始在巴士营办商打击
the focus the busy i-95 corridor from New York to Florida
重点在繁忙的I-95走廊从纽约到佛罗里达州
you know the deal cheap roughly 40 discount bus companies out of business
你知道这笔交易大约便宜40折扣巴士公司歇业
it's not clear the Boston today was hired by the church for owned by the church churches operate buses
它今天不明确的波士顿被聘为由教会由教会教堂拥有公交车运营
you're not bus companies they don't have professional drivers in many cases they dont pray to the same standard the professional bus companies do
你不是巴士公司，他们没有专业的司机在他们不祈求同一标准的专业巴士公司做很多情况下，
tonight in north eastern Tennessee with so many dead i-40 is expected to remain shutdown well into the night
今晚在北东田纳西州有这么多死的i-40预计将保持关断到深夜
Tom Costello NBC News Washington
汤姆·科斯特洛NBC新闻华盛顿
the FBI today shutdown what is calling the most sophisticated internet site in the business of selling hard drugs including heroin cocaine and LSD what they say was a robust big money and completely illegal business on the web
美国联邦调查局今天关机是什么调用最先进的互联网网站在销售硬毒品，包括可卡因海洛因和LSD他们说什么是一个健壮的大资金，并在网络上完全违法经营的业务
are justice correspondent Pete Williams following the story for us in our DC news room tonight the creep
是正义的记者皮特·威廉斯下面的故事我们在特区新闻室今晚蠕变
Brian FBI agency in closing in on this operation for 2 years even making over a hundred percent of illegal drugs from the side and have it all ship to the min New York
在结束对这一操作2年甚至使过非法毒品从侧面百分百并拥有这一切的船到最小纽约布赖恩联邦调查局代理
anyone trying to log on to the website today found this notice shut down by the FBI but when was running federal prosecutor say the website
任何人试图在今天登录到网站上找到此通知关闭联邦调查局，但是当运行被联邦检察官说，网站
the Silk Road was the internets biggest Bazaar for illegal drugs and international marketplace with the sideline in illegal hacking software
丝绸之路是非法毒品和国际市场上具有非法黑客软件边线的互连网最大的巴扎
prosecutors reveal today that they arrested the man the accuser running the site Ross William Ulbricht of San Francisco a 29 year old with degrees in physics and engineering
检察官今天透露，他们逮捕了原告运行旧金山的现场罗斯威廉·乌布利希一个29岁与学位物理学和工程学的男人
he was a dream for drug users because he was very technically adapted he was able to hide photos
他是一个梦想，吸毒者，因为他非常技术上适应他能躲照片
the website that he put together and the actual sales of illegal drugs that the drug sellers would make on his website
他放在一起的网站和非法药物的实际销售该药品销售商会使他的网站
investigator say in the two and a half years it was operating it generated roughly 1.2 billion dollars in sales with nearly 960
研究者说，在两年半的时间里它被运行，它产生的大约120十亿美元的销售额近960
court documents say the site Ridge cellars to vacuum seal packages to avoid detection by k9 or Lectronic sniffers
法庭文件说，该网站岭酒窖，以真空密封包装，以避免检测由K9或Lectronic嗅探器
energy buyers to have shipments into someone else is a friends house or PO Box
能源买家有出货到别人是一个朋友的家里或邮政信箱
investigator say it was an online market for virtually any illegal drug imaginable including heroin cocaine LSD in methamphetamine
调查人员说，这是一个在线的市场几乎任何非法毒品甲基苯丙胺可以想象的包括海洛因可卡因LSD
the FBI says this ad from the side of road high quality heroin all rock conveniently vacuum seal a reporter for Forbes magazine road in August about buying marijuana of the Silk Road website
联邦调查局说，这个广告从道路高质量海洛因的一侧的所有岩石方便真空密封记者在八月福布斯杂志的道路有关购买丝路网站的大麻
solutely where was side of face professional dancer seamless the college experience
solutely在哪里面的专业舞蹈演员侧无缝的大学生活
prosecutor sale Brook called himself Dread Pirate Roberts after a character in a movie they also accusing of offering money to have a user of the site killed who was threatening to expose to get her say that was never carried out
检察官销售布鲁克称自己在电影中，他们还指责提供资金把杀该网站谁威胁要揭露，让她说，从来没有进行过的用户的一个字符后恐惧海盗罗伯茨
the Williams in DC for us tonight Pizza X as you may know for days now Israel's prime minister Benjamin Netanyahu Lisbon warning the world of the new president of Iran
威廉姆斯在DC为我们今晚比萨X作为你可能知道现在天以色列总理本雅明·内塔尼亚胡里斯本警告伊朗新总统的世界
is just a wolf in sheep's clothing with his surprising semen candid in conciliatory talk about Iran nuclear program tonight hearing
是披着羊皮的只是一个狼与他的惊人的精液在对伊朗核计划今晚和解听证会坦诚的谈话
address the you win this week Netanyahu is showing he is keeping up the pressure in an interview with Archie foreign affairs correspondent Andrea Mitchell
解决这个星期你就赢了内塔尼亚胡正显示出他是紧跟在与阿奇外交事务记者安德里亚·米切尔接受采访时的压力
everybody knows everyone wants to destroy Israel Richmond
大家都知道每个人都希望毁灭以色列里士满
trying to build a box for that
试图建立一个方块为
you don't want to be a position where this Masonic apocalyptic radical regimes that has these wild ambition with my spokes good to wear with building the weapons of mass death
你不想成为这个地方的共济会大难临头激进的政权具有这些狼子野心与我的辐条好穿与建筑群死亡的武器的位置
Julie's with radically different versions of the same world stage this week is Reelz Prime Minister Netanyahu Iran president rouhani cannot be trusted
朱莉与完全不同版本的同一世界舞台本周是Reelz总理内塔尼亚胡伊朗总统rouhani不能被信任
do you think you have a risk of overstating the dangers
你觉得你有拔高的危险的危险
hurting Israel bite isolated from the rest of the world that wants to know
伤害以色列咬从世界各地想知​​道的分离
no I wanted to put solution of wonder actually this model 001 a test will we are and I think the important thing is not what he says the weather we get a full dismantling of Iran
不，我想把奇迹的解决方案实际上这个模型001测试会我们，我认为重要的不是他说什么天气，我们得到伊朗的全面拆解
253 election day to be model
253选举日是模型
what is that a free to go because of this was you been going blue jeans how many people there any people to join the protester
什么是一个自由的，因为这个原因去了你一直去蓝色牛仔裤有多少人有任何人加入抗议者
but they don't have that the government not funny the governed by a Tola he has a cult that called
但他们没有，政府不好笑的管辖由陀他有一个邪教调用
is wild incense Griffin
野香格里芬
tell me he is willing to give diplomacy a chance
告诉我，他愿意给外交一个机会
as long as the US keep the pressure on a round and even with the US government on the brink of shutting down on Monday the Israeli respect our President Obama living the same message to him
只要美国继续圆，甚至与美国政府关闭，周一以色列尊重我们的总统奥巴马生活在同一个消息到他的边缘压力
InterMetro here with us in New York tonight Andrea facts
这里InterMetro与我们在纽约今晚安德烈事实
we have late were Justin was tonight from Southern California to Michael Jackson wrongful death trial after 5 months of testimony
我们已经是晚期今晚贾斯汀是从南加州到迈克尔·杰克逊过失致人死亡审判5个月后的证词
free has just found the hcg live the concert promoter of Jackson's final concert or should not be held liable the singer's death
免费刚刚发现HCG住杰克逊的最后一场音乐会的演唱会宣传或不应该被追究法律责任歌手的死亡
Jackson's mother is three children have filed a suit arguing the AG live negligently higher Conrad Murray is Jackson's personal doctor in orange signs the Jacksons health West Imperial rating Dr Murray was convicted of involuntary manslaughter for giving Jackson MS
杰克逊的母亲是三个孩子已经提起诉讼，主张对AG住疏忽更高莫里是杰克逊的私人医生在橙色标志杰克逊的健康西御评级穆雷医生被判犯过失杀人罪给密西西比州杰克逊
powerful dose of propofol that killed him in June of 2009 still have for us tonight new developments in the investigation
强大的剂量异丙酚是杀害了他在2009年六月仍然有调查我们今晚的新发展
videos getting so much attention and talk to motorcycle swimming around a driver with this family in the car and later the unbelievable signed the Fox in one city walk up to this morning the submarine sticking up for the paper
影片获得如此多的关注和倾诉摩托车四处游动这个家庭司机在车上，后来难以置信签署了福克斯在一个城市走到今天早晨潜艇粘起来的纸
is a scary and grizzly pizza video and if you've ever been driving a car and found yourself in a swarm of oncoming motorcycles have Maalox
是一个可怕的和灰熊的比萨视频，如果你曾经驾驶一辆车，发现自己的摩托车迎面而来的一大群具有抗酸药
Amil your b*** what happened in New York this weekend Tokunaga LeeAnn via lantern MSNBC Stephanie Gosk reports is repeated all across this country
阿米尔您的B ***通过什么灯笼MSNBC的斯蒂芬妮Gosk发生在纽约这个周末德永LEEANN报告是所有在这个国家反复
motorcycle chase a family with a small child Manhattan Westside 911 calls
摩托车追逐一个家庭有一个小的孩子曼哈顿西区911电话
what Indian tourist visa black SUV
什么印度旅游签证黑色的SUV
the writers of the business executives windows pulled from the car and beat him his wife and child were on her
从车上拉又打了他的妻子和孩子的企业高管窗口作家们对她的
what are the ledge motorcycle is Christopher Cruz was arranged for today charged with reckless driving and on waffle imprisonment
什么是窗台摩托车克里斯托弗·克鲁斯被安排为今天被控鲁莽驾驶和华夫监禁
cruisin the other motorcyclist JCSU V after his bike was bump stops short in front of vehicle
在车前CRUISIN其他电单车JCSU V后面他的自行车是撞击停止短
nothing to do with the 74th Street
无关，与第74街
the family of Edwin Mieses is another rider severely injured and possibly paralyzed when he was run over by the SUV
埃德温Mieses的家庭是另一个车手严重受伤，并可能瘫痪，当他被越野车碾过
is defending the group
是保卫组
what 14050 around the country say these groups are growing in numbers
什么14050全国各地的说，这些群体也越来越号码
videos are posted online movies
视频被发布到网上的电影
Dallas Riders toys in pursuit in San Francisco motorcyclist breakthrough
追求在旧金山骑摩托车的突破达拉斯骑士玩具
Lisa in St Louis riders take over the highway TV
丽莎在圣路易斯车手接管公路电视
chasing big is a crazy the day bakery in danger of cells and others sentences with simple damage the engine
追大是一个疯狂的日子面包店在细胞和其他句子的简单损害危险的引擎
go out
出
New York State Trooper Heather sync with a bridge for trouble for motorcycle group every weekend when weather is nice
纽约州警官希瑟与摩托车组时遇到问题的桥梁同步，每到周末的时候天气晴朗
are they as a group
是他们作为一个群体
motorcycles CBR 150 plus 100
摩托车CBR 150加100
New York City more likely still fighting it shine a light on a growing nation wide problem Stephanie Gosk NBC News New York
纽约市更可能仍然战斗用光芒照耀它的成长全国性的问题斯蒂芬妮Gosk NBC新闻纽约
when we come back here tonight the controversy over what's happening on some of the nation's most hallowed ground
当我们回到这里，今晚的争论发生了什么事就一些国家的最神圣的理由
controversy among some of the families of those buried at Arlington National Cemetery following a forced cleanup of the area known as section 60
在一些那些埋葬在阿灵顿国家公墓以下称为第60区的强制清理的家庭争议
is the burial ground for over 800 of the recent dead from ROC recent wars in Iraq and Afghanistan along with veterans from other wars until recently was full of momento that many of the grave sights
是坟墓在近期死亡800从我国近代战争在伊拉克和阿富汗以及来自其他战争的老兵，直至最近才充满时代报的，许多坟墓景点
as one Washington Post writer describe in a living memorial Aurora Messi burial ground of war still being fought
为一体华盛顿邮报作家在描述一个活生生的纪念碑战争极光梅西墓地仍在进行
the cemetery has now in Bartow ever on a full scale cleaning saving summer Mentos and storage
墓地现在已经在巴托曾经在一个全面的清洁节能夏天曼妥思和存储
but it was decided it had to be kept the same cleanliness standard as the rest of the cemetery another note hear the government shutdown has also shutdown us cemeteries overseas including the vast EDH a cemetery in Norman
但它决定它必须保持相同的洁净度标准，墓地的其余部分别注听取政府关机也关断我们的墓地，包括海外的广大EDH在诺曼底墓地
Southwest Airlines has an ounce of fire the captain of the 737 the land of nose first of New York's LaGuardia Airport this past ally 9 people were injured that day air traffic with bottle up for hours
西南航空公司有火每盎司737的队长鼻子的土地的首次纽约的拉瓜迪亚机场在过去的盟友9人受伤那天空中交通瓶了好几个小时
banal former captain with a 13 year veteran with the airline with over twelve thousand hours of flight time
平庸的前队长与一名13岁的老将与航空公司有一万两千个小时的飞行时间
we now have the first pictures from space of the newest island on earth this was the one we told you about formed in the wake of the earthquake in hat in Pakistan just over a week ago the island is about 70 feet above sea level is appear from the ocean floor offshore
我们现在有来自太空的第一张照片是地球上最新的岛屿，这是我们告诉你关于形成在地震中的帽子在巴基斯坦刚刚超过一个星期前岛是约70英尺以上的海平面之后的一个是从出现海底近海
geologist say these islands are often formed by searching mud and they often disappear over time because they getting road head by the constant action of ocean waves
地质学家说，这些岛屿往往是通过搜索泥形成，他们往往随着时间而消失，因为他们得到路头被海浪不断的行动
an extraordinary site visible on a small barrier island in northwestern Alaska
非凡的网站上的一个小屏障岛西北部的阿拉斯加可见
the dark area between the snow in the water that would be solid walrus its been called the great wall restaurant out of 2013 an estimated 10000 of the animals and remember they are not small some of them grow away is much is a car
雪在水中，这将是坚实的海象之间的暗区其被称为长城餐厅出2013年的动物的估计10000，记住他们不是小了一些他们的成长路程是多少是一辆车
speculation is the Gathering that b**** because of Gwendoline ice options in Alaska this time of year
炒作是聚会，B，因为在阿拉斯加的Gwendoline冰选项****每年的这个时候
Anna shocking site in Milan Italy as people in the old section of the city woke up this morning to find
在意大利米兰安娜令人震惊的网站，因为人们在城市的老款今早醒来时发现
that a submarine head surfaced in the middle of the street
该潜艇的头在街道中间浮出水面
crashing through the pavement narrowly missing a car sailors were seen scurrying out of the connington hour but when you stop and think about the fact that there is
通过路面轰然差点砸到一辆车水手们看到乱窜了connington小时，但是当你停下来思考的事实，那就是
ocean beneath the streets of Milan you realize what an artful hoax it was an elaborate publicity stunt for an insurance company
海洋米兰的街道下你明白什么是巧妙的骗局这是一个精心制作的宣传噱头一家保险公司
when we come back here tonight remembering a master one of the all time great names behind some great stories of suspense
当我们回到这里，今晚记忆高手背后的一些很有悬念的故事，所有的时间伟大的名字之一
for anyone who has ever passed by a bookstore say nothing of his millions of fans Tom Clancy's name has always been synonymous with a good gripping yarn
对于谁曾经路过一家书店的人说他的数百万球迷汤姆克兰西的名字一直等同于一个良好的握持纱线
as authors go he was a master is form he was an iconoclast to be sure and over the years he uses bath while teas to buy a tank and a by partial ownership stake in his beloved Baltimore Orioles
作为作者去，他是一个大师是形式，他是一个反传统的，以确保多年来，他用洗澡而茶买了罐和在他心爱的巴尔的摩金莺部分所有权股权
Tom Clancy died today at the age of 66 we have a look back tonight from NBC's Mike Tice
汤姆克兰西今天在66岁去世，我们回头看看今晚从美国全国广播公司的Mike泰斯
Sean Connery and Alec Baldwin James Earl Jones Harrison Ford and Ben Affleck delete actors who short list of career highlights with rolled in the movie versions of Tom Clancy novels
肖恩·康纳利和亚历克·鲍德温詹姆斯·厄尔·琼斯哈里森·福特和本·阿弗莱克删除演员谁的职业生涯的短名单突出了与轧制汤姆克兰西小说的电影版本
is a pulsating yarns were always a real star
是一个脉动纱线总是一个真正的明星
long with his uncanny military hardware and spy game tactics Juliet
长期与他离奇的军事硬件和谍战战术朱丽叶
books every hotel stories is the third eye tracking current
本书每一家酒店的故事是第三眼跟踪电流
oppression free smart bomb was in common use plants use one in clear and present danger to take out a meeting of drug cartel leader
压迫免费智能炸弹是普遍使用的植物使用一个清楚而现实的危险拿出的贩毒集团领导人会议
and in Patriot Games is Jack Ryan hero tickets to the CIA's inner sanctum what satellite tracking in real time should an anti terrorist attack old military professionals monkeys many fans often wondered what class you writing from classified information
而在爱国者游戏是杰克·瑞恩英雄门票中情局的内部密室什么卫星实时跟踪应防恐怖袭击老军人的猴子很多球迷经常在想，你从分类信息类写作
it seems as if Clancy was running from inside the military he was very smart extremely well read in 4c was a great plot twist
它好像克兰西是从军事内部运行，他非常聪明非常好读4c中获得了巨大的剧情转折
classy roll over two dozen bestsellers
优雅卷超过两打的畅销书